Betraying little witch...
Yeah...
That's a perfect name for me.
#2 "The Princess's Confession"
I mean, the Koiwais,
the servants of the Adagaki family,
are pretty famous for that.
Wouldn't this be going against
your master's wishes?
I'm Adagaki Aki's fiancé.
You're ignoring your master and secretly
meeting with Makabe Masamune.
I wonder what they'd say if
they ever found out about that.
Sure, why not?
If you want to snitch on me, go ahead.
Wow... I guess that didn't hurt at all.
Unfortunately, no.
Oh, by the way, when I said "them,"
I didn't mean Aki-chan.
I was talking about your parents.
I mean, honestly, your feelings
are pretty understandable.
Because you're like me.
You...
Aki-chan's pretty pure, too.
I'm pretty sure I'll have no
problem winning her over.
But if the families get involved,
things will be different.
You can't break away from
the status you were born into.
Not even a step.
I mean, if you could,
you wouldn't come all the way to Paris
dealing with this warped
master-servant relationship.
Don't speak as if you know me.
I'm only doing what I'm doing
because you're unworthy of Aki-sama.
I've thought that ever since you
appeared at the Adagaki home.
You're so conniving.
Oh? And how am I conniving, exactly?
I very much plan on bringing
some grandchildren into the world.
That's not what I'm talking about!
You're acting like someone who's
precious to Aki-sama and lyi—
Are you going to say it?
Don't blame me if they
find out about that thing.
See?
You saying those things just because you
don't like me really won't get through to me.
But anyway, your parents are pissed.
They're wondering what you're doing,
skipping out on work like this.
You should probably lay low for a while
so they don't relieve you
of your attendant duties.
Show how it's done?
How are we supposed to do that?
C-Calm down, me! How lame
would I be if I lost my cool here?
In the end, this is just part
of the Dead or Love plan.
I just need to take the lead!
Hey—
Let's go for a little walk.
Right...
I see. It seems like they're really going for it.
It's very clear that you're working hard to
lessen the distance between you two, it is.
This French girl doesn't hold back!
What a beautiful city...
Next...
Why, yes...
What do we do next?
I never thought I'd be walking
side by side with you like this.
Me, neither.
Next, let's wander around Akiba.
There will be anime, games,
and manga waiting for us there!
When I'm with you, I could walk
to the end of the Mansei Bridge!
Could you stop awkwardly dubbing over us?
Aw, but I thought it was a good idea, I did.
You can let your creativity run free after
you get the basic shape of this drama down.
My hand is sweating so much!
Crap, crap, crap.
Did she notice I'm actually nervous?
Huh? The one that wasn't
holding her hand is fine?
Listen carefully, Muriel.
Stop butting in. Take a few more steps back.
A-All right, then...
I guess the Cruel Princess is
doing the best she can, too...
Honestly...
Let's continue this already.
Okay...
I see...
I get it!
Huh? Wh-What is it?
You're shameless, you stupid Makabe!
Oh, are you out of gas?
I want to end myself...
Er, it's not that big of a deal...
Anyway, why don't we go get something to eat?
Together.
Food. Energy. Sugar. Carbohydrates.
Well, she's not saying no.
Took you long enough, Makabe!
Sorry. You're okay with mustard
on your sandwich, ri—
Hey... You think we should
just eat these like usual?
What?!
I mean... Muriel's staring really hard.
Right...
Maybe we should do something rom-com-like.
She did say to show her how it's done.
But what are we supposed to do?
Maybe we should feed each other.
Wait, I don't have ulterior motives!
If you have any other ideas...
No, I don't! I don't have any at all!
Then, uh, let's go with the feeding thing.
Yes, yes! That's a great idea!
Here... Open wide, Makabe-kun...
H-How nice of you... Adagaki-san...
I-It's so hard to eat...
Th-Thanks for the food...
I don't have time for this shit!
Oh?
I can't... Why the hell do I have to do this?!
I'd rather eat it myself than feed it to him!
Sorry, Muriel, but this is our limit.
Nope. I can't give you this.
Jeanne!
Toutes mes excusez, mademoiselle.
Excusez moi!
You always did like them.
Huh?
Dogs, especially big ones.
Did I ever mention that before?
We used to have big dogs, but...
Used to? What about now?
I haven't had any since we lost our last one.
I couldn't bring myself to get a new one.
I see... So those were the last ones.
This is the perfect opportunity,
so will you just listen for a bit?
Before, I wasn't a big eater or anything.
How I ended up like this...
and why I can't accept your feelings...
I'll tell you everything now.
You mustn't, Aki-sama.
I can't see her?
We don't want you getting chickenpox, too.
Well, that's boring.
I wanted to have fun playing
with makeup with Yoshino again.
Are you really blaming all this on me?!
You always do this!
Just shut up! I've had enough of you!
You always run away like that!
You're always so selfish!
Just think for a damn second!
I'm the one who's had enough...
Why did I ever get married
to someone like you?
Sean! Lancelot! Come here!
Oh, hey! That tickles!
I guess you're my only friends today.
No, that's plenty.
Sean?
You can't get away now.
You put us through too much trouble!
M-My family's really rich!
You moron. Then treat us to something.
Sean, get them!
What do you think you're doing
in front of my house?
Uh-oh!
Let's go!
What's your name?
I'm asking you for your name.
I-I'm... Masamune.
You look awful. Wipe off your face.
Fank you...
Who blows their nose at a time like this?!
Huh? Should I not have?
S-Sorry... I'll wash it and return it to you.
I don't want it anymore.
It's fine! Stop crying!
That was how Masamune and I met.
There you are, Aki.
Snow White
Want to go to dinner with me?
Just the two of us?
Yes, it'll be a little date.
No. Don't wear that outfit.
Really?
Let's go have some clothes made for you.
There's a designer
I always request outfits from.
Just the two of us?
Yes.
I guess all three of us going isn't an option...
So whoever gets my affection wins?
Aki-chan, this is to thank
you for the other day.
Chocolate from Patisserie Otafuku.
They only make ten of these a day!
Isn't that amazing?
I'm honestly tired of stuff like this.
Huh?! But why?
My mom and dad aren't getting along.
They only start fighting about
how much presents cost or how rare
they are when they want to win my favor.
It's so lame. I'm just sick of it.
O-Oh, no...
You don't need to cry.
You can eat them if you want.
B-But I feel so bad for you, Aki-chan...
I would be really sad if my mom
and dad didn't get along...
I wouldn't want that!
You're so nice...
Masamune.
A-Ahi-hyan?!
But you're too weak.
You need to toughen up a bit.
Masamune, I'll train you so you
won't lose to those bullies anymore.
Huh?
Lancelot!
Save me!
I don't remember the last
time I laughed this much.
Okay, look this way.
Lancelot, sit.
Okay, now you try.
G-Good boy... Good boy...
See?
With my guidance, Masamune
grew a little stronger every day...
and every day became fun for me.
But...
Where are you, Tubbymune?!
You've got some nerve bailing
after you called us out here!
Come to the park
tomorrow at 5 PM.
-Masamune
I'm right here.
Hey, what are you doing up there?
I'm sick and tired of everything.
Today's the last day you'll ever bully me.
I've also left a will.
Everything you've done
to me will come to light.
Goodbye, you embarrassments.
H-Hey!
Crap!
What is this?
You tricked us!
Ow! Dang it!
That was a huge success.
Who do you think you are?!
You finish them off.
Man, that hurt!
Okay.
I'm not scared of you guys anymore.
They should stop bothering you now.
It's all thanks to you, Aki-chan.
I never would've been able
to do this on my own.
I just helped you out a little bit.
I want you, at least, to be happy.
Huh?
It's hopeless for me.
My parents are separating.
Aki-chan...
H-Huh? That's weird.
This time, it's my turn.
I'm going to keep supporting you
so you can cheer up.
I'll stay by your side!
So... what happened after that?
Nothing. He never showed his face again.
Huh?!
I guess he just wanted someone
to save him from the bullies.
I just ended up having feelings for him.
But... I really did like him.
His puffy cheeks,
his tubby tummy... everything.
Ever since I cried and started binge eating,
I just couldn't stop overeating,
and I'm tired of it.
And I guess Masamune didn't feel
bad about disappearing, either.
H-How do you know?
Well, he told me himself.
Huh?
Gasou Kanetsugu...
He used to be kind like that
when we were younger, too.
Masamune is his old nickname.
The Cruel Princess thinks Gasou is me?
Wait, before that...
Everything she said is completely
different from my memories.
I don't ever want to feel that sad again.
So... that's why I can't accept
your feelings toward me.
What is she talking about?
Feel sad?
You're the one who chased me away, saying
you could never have feelings for me!
You called me Pig's Foot!
That's why... I...
There!
Aki-chan was crying...
I hope this cheers her up a little.
Hey, Tubbymune!
We need to thank you for the other day.
Hey, wait!
Almost... I'm almost at Aki-chan's house...
Aki-chan!
Hold it!
What the hell's this?
Give it back!
They're filthy!
Aki-chan! Aki-chan!
This loser's trying to get that
boss girl to save him again?
Talk about pathetic!
No! Aki-chan's not like that!
I promised her I'd stay by her side!
We're going to be friends forever and—
Shut up, you stupid boys.
Aki-cha—
I'll never fall in love with you,
Pig's Foot.
Talk about sad!
He just got shot down!
She called him Pig's Foot!
Aki-chan...
The Dead or Love plan...
Making her fall for me, then dumping her.
Adagaki Aki actually did the
exact same thing to me first!
So how is she able to look
like the tragic heroine here?!
You can't be serious.
Then why did you call me
"Pig's Foot" and chase me away?
What are you talking about?
Quit acting like the victim!
You deserved everything you got!
Non! What is the meaning of this?
Fighting is bad, it is!
This is just too cruel.
I thought you'd at least hear me out.
Masamune! Aki left! Aren't you
going to chase after her?
Sorry...
But I can't think about anything right now.
Money is important! Money is important!
What's the matter, Aki-chan?
What happened?
I'd be happy to listen, Ak—
What the heck happened?
What is it, Nii-san?
Where the hell are those
stupid Japanese kids?!
I thought they were supposed to
teach you the essence of rom-coms!
We ran into a bit of trouble,
so it's been canceled.
I'll talk to them again and make them—
If you do that, I'll hate you!
Nii-san, I'm going to draw a new manga.
One that has a happy ending.
Makabe-kun! You're safe!
Yeah.
We were so worried!
Where's Aki-sama?
She's...
We sort of...
got into a fight.
Message
Koiwai
Edit
Do you understand what you've done?
You need to know your place.
I'm sorry.
For the time being, as punishment,
you will not be allowed to go out.
I understand.
Aki-sama.
I've been looking for you, Stupid Yoshino.
Are you crying?
I did this for her
eight years ago, too.